https://www.ozscopes.com.au/privacy-notice/

Due to limited stock availability, please contact our Customer Service at
1800 SCOPES (1800 726 737) for stock enquiry and to ensure your order arrives by Christmas.
Stores Network
1800 SCOPES (1800 726 737)
OZScopes - Online Shopping
Menu
TelescopesTelescope By TypesReflector TelescopeRefractor TelescopeDobsonian TelescopeCassegrain TelescopeOptical Tube Assemblies (OTA)Solar TelescopeAll TelescopesTelescope By BrandsSkywatcher TelescopesMeade TelescopesSaxon TelescopesCelestron TelescopesAccessoriesTelescope MountsAltazimuth (AZ) MountsEquatorial (EQ) MountsAltazimuth-Equatorial (AZ-EQ) MountComputerized (GOTO) MountsMount AccessoriesEyepieces & FiltersFiltersSky-Watcher EyepiecesMeade EyepiecesBaader EyepiecesSaxon EyepiecesCelestron EyepiecesEyepieces and Filter KitsAstrophotographyAstronomy CamerasT-Rings and AdaptersDigital Camera & Smartphone AdaptersGuidersOther Astroimaging AccessoriesVisual AccessoriesBarlow LensesDiagonalsFinderscopesCollimatorsFocal ReducersGeneral AccessoriesNavigation AccessoriesPower SuppliesHard CasesAstronomy PublicationsOther AccessoriesSport Optics AccessoriesTripodsBinocular AccessoriesSpotting Scope AccessoriesNight Vision AccessoriesBinocularsFeatured BrandsBushnell BinocularsVortex BinocularsCelestron BinocularsVanguard BinocularsSteiner BinocularsNikon BinocularsLeica BinocularsMeade BinocularsAlpen BinocularsZeiss BinocularsLeupold BinocularsYukon BinocularsSaxon BinocularsBinocular by TypesAstronomy / Night BinocularsCompact BinocularsMarine BinocularsBirdwatching BinocularsZoom BinocularsHunting BinocularsALL BINOCULARSBundle DealsNight VisionNight Vision By TypesNight Vision MonocularsNight Vision BinocularsThermal Imaging ScopesALL NIGHT VISIONFeatured BrandsYukon Night VisionPulsar Night VisionBushnell Night VisionLeupold Night VisionSpotting ScopesSpotting Scope by TypesStraight Spotting ScopeAngled Spotting ScopeAll Spotting ScopesFeatured BrandsVortex Spotting ScopeBushnell Spotting ScopeLeica Spotting ScopeVanguard Spotting ScopeAcuter Spotting ScopeMeade Spotting ScopesAlpen Spotting ScopeYukon Spotting ScopeLeupold Spotting ScopeMicroscopesMicroscopesBiological MicroscopesGemological MicroscopesDigital MicroscopesCompound MicroscopesStereo MicroscopesMagnifiers and LoupesSpecimens & SlidesAccessoriesMiscellaneousHunting Optics & AccessoriesRifle ScopesRings and MountsCaps and CoversBoresighterShooting RestsHunting KnivesSpotlightsMonocularsRangefinderTrail CameraBagsOptics Cleaning KitsSALETelescopesMountsBinocularsSpotting ScopeHuntingNight VisionMicroscopesTelescope AccessoriesOthers
Brands
A
Acuter
Alpen Optics
Astrovisuals
Athlon Optics
B
Baader
Privacy Notice
Thank you for visiting our website and reviewing our privacy policy. This site collects information about you for monitoring purposes and uses this information to improve the website to better meet user needs. Some information is also collected for statistical and research purposes.
When you choose to send us a completed electronic form that includes your personal details we collect personal information, such as your name, address and email address. This will only be used for the purpose you provided it and we will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.
We ask you about your ethnic origin/gender/age/employment status so that we can understand how responsive this program is to people from diverse backgrounds/of different gender/according to their age/in relation to their current employment for research purposes. This information is kept separate from information that identifies you. You do not have to provide this information and not providing this information will not affect your use of this website and access to our services in any way.
Logged information is not disclosed outside our staff or those under contract to conduct maintenance to web server components. We make no attempt to identify individuals from these records unless it is necessary to the investigation of a breach of law.
We will only publish information on this site when it has been collected for that purpose or with your consent.
Through our web monitoring service provider, the website uses cookies to provide information that assist us in making the site more useable. Cookies are small data files that we send to your computer so we can record usage statistics about the Channel, such as number of visits, unique visits, documents viewed, browser type, and the way the site is navigated. More information on cookies can be found on Cookie Central http://www.cookiecentral.com/
Once you leave this site and go to another site a different privacy statement is likely to apply and therefore you should check the security of the new website.
If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving OZHut marketing material. You can opt-out by clicking on unsubscribe or contact us.
If you have any concerns about providing the information requested or if you want to access the information we hold about you please don't hesitate to contact us.
Customer Service
FAQ
Shipping Information
Returns
Store Location
About Us
About Us
OZHut Stores Network
Privacy Notice
Terms & Conditions
Company Info
Call Us 1800 SCOPES (1800 726 737)
support@ozscopes.com.au
OZScopes is a premium optics shop based in Croydon South, Victoria. We supply all types of telescopes, sport optics, and related accessories at affordable prices. All our products sold are genuine and fully-backed by an Australian warranty. Shop with us today!
© 2019-2020 - OZhut Pty Ltd - All Rights Reserved - ABN: 68 131 981 087
